enlightened.rocks 2018-09-11

# Enlightened rocks

### Cookies, Tracking and Third-party tools

This website utilises "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Some cookies are necessary for the operation of our website, if you choose to block them some aspects of the site may not work for you. With your login you allow us to set cookies in your browser. 

Single subpages may contain code from Google+ which could track your visits to that specific site. That feature is used to allow user to quickly share event advertisment on Google+. There is also a G+ applet for inviters to give a quick access to their circles. If these applets set cookies or use tracking technologies it is out of our responsibility. 

We do not use tracking code on the website itself, no Google Analytics, no Piwik, no New Relic. 

We utilize the power of content delivery networks by using cloudflare.com. This service is using a cookie to keep your connection to enlightened.rocks stable and consistent. It is neccessary for good performance on delivering static assets to your browser regardless of your location. 

### Personal data

After you confirm the Google login consent we will pull personal data from Google+ API. We fetch the following fields for persistent storage in your account: 

  * Google-ID
  * Connected e-mail address
  * Full name
  * Profile picture
  * Profile URL

This data will recieve updates every time you actively login on enlightened.rocks. No periodic updates happen in the background. 

This website asks for personal data like home town, postal code or your language. If you do not want to enter that data, you won't have to. It will only be used for Enlightened event planning and Ingress related apps and never be sold or gifted to third parties without your explicit permission. Connected Enlightened applications may receive parts of your data and store it on their databases. Usually that will happen if you use Enlightened related Telegram bots. Please keep in mind: It's the task of the bot owner to inform you about the storage of personal data. 

You can export the data linked to your account here once every 30 days.

You can delete all your saved data including your account here.

### Hosting

Your data is stored on servers in Germany or France, in datacenters with a high level of security. Database access is only possible for the website owner and never for the hosting company. 

### Data usage

For planning purposes other Enlightened agents may gain access to read your data. These agents have to confirm every 90 days to adhere to this privacy policy. They are not allowed to export or send data to third parties with the exception of Niantic, Google Drive or messenger apps needed to plan events. Using the data after the event has passed is disallowed and prevented through technical means wherever possible. 

Other websites may gain access to your data with your explicit consent through oAuth2 interfaces. You can revoke that permission any time in your profile. 

enlightened.rocks also features personal profile pages. You can control and hide personal data in your profile settings. 

### Disclaimer

This policy is only valid for content created and provided by the website's owner. It does not apply for any other linked website, Telegram bots besides RocksBot or assets.
